# 前一段时间 大家都在自己的家里做面食
A while back, everyone tries to made food made by flour at their homes
# 这个是我在超市里 唯一能够买到的酵母
This is the only yeast I can get at the supermarket
# 我们要继续做一些发酵的食品
We're going to continue to make some fermented foods
# 昨天在超市里 看到有人在卖蜂蜜大麻花
Yesterday at the supermarket, I saw someone selling fired honey dough twist
# 真的是特别诱人
It looks really delicious
# 我们今天就要做 蜂蜜大麻花
So today, we are going to make the honey dough twist
# 做大麻花 材料都差不多 就是
Ingredients we need are these
# 面粉 蜂蜜 鸡蛋 白糖 油
Flour, honey, eggs, sugar, and oil
# 把这些材料弄好 炸出来就可以了
Once we prepared those materials, we just need to fry the honey twist
# 像我做东西 各部分的食材之间
When I cook, among those ingredients
# 没有一个很好的配比
I don't have a good mix formula
# 大部分都是自己觉得合适然后就放进去
Just putting ingredients what I think may fit in
# 我今天是用的黄油
Today, I am using the butter
# 也可以加一些其它的没有很重味道的油
It can be substituted to other tasteless cooking oils
# 都是可以的
Substituting is ok
# 在全国 其实有很多这种卖大麻花的店
There are lots of shops for selling fried dough twists in China
# 生意真的很火爆
And these shops are doing good business
# 现在面已经揉得差不多了
# It's almost kneaded now
# 可以把它放在盆里发酵了
It's ready to ferment in a bowl
# （玩会游戏）
(Playing)
# 这个是咱们发的面 白胖白胖的
This is our fermented flour. It’s fat and while
# 里面蜂窝孔还是很可以的嘛
The honeycomb inside looks good
# 雪鱼这是第一次做
This is my first time to cook this
# 面发的还是可以的
I do a good job at fermenting flour this time
# 上案板
Taking out the cutting board
# 还得站起来（身高不够）
I have to stand up to do this (not tall enough. lol)
# 再揉一下吧
Let’s Knead the dough for a little more time
# 这个面因为加了牛奶 鸡蛋
Because we put mike, eggs
# 还有油的原因
and oil into the flour
# 所以揉起来还是感觉比平时的面
The dough is softer than the usual
# 更软乎一些
# 而且有这种滑润的感觉
And touch smooth
# 其实做这些东西 我觉得特别有成就感
Every time when I making this kind of food, I feel proud of
# 因为你要亲自参与它的制作过程
Because we need to patriciate in the making process
# 这样吃起来会不会更香呢
With our own participation, it may taste better
# 倒油 准备炸
Let’s putting oil and start to fry
# 哎呀（麻花）散开了
Oh, the twist falls apart
# 它上面没有捏紧 所以说
So if we do not tight the dough twist up
# 炸的时候会散开
It will fall apart when frying it
# 咱们先炸的是 两个小的麻花
First, we fry two small dough twist
# 是个头比较小
These are quite small
# 是用单股面做成的麻花
It twisted by the single dough noddle
# 其它的那几个比较长的麻花
But these longer dough twists
# 都是两根面搓成一个
Are twisted by two dough noodles
# 第一次吃蜂蜜大麻花时
The first time I ate the honey dough twist
# 那时还没有工作
I did not have a job
# 一个蜂蜜大麻花 好像是两块五吧
At that time, it cost about 2.5 RMB
# 但是觉得特别好吃
But it tastes so good
# 那种好吃就是
Because it has
# 有牛奶的香味 还有蜂蜜的甜味
Milk and sweet honey
# 两者就是交织在一起 味道特别棒
The combination favors are so good
# 后来 虽然说 遇到很多大麻花
Even since that, I tried more another dough twist
# 但是 吃起来确实没有最开始的美味了
I cannot find good tastes like the first time
# 这个是最不好看的这一个
This is the ugliest one
# 看这一个个粗壮如大锁链子
Look at them. They're as big as chains
# 这就是我做的蜂蜜大麻花
This is my honey dough twist
# 这次咱们做的麻花有几个失败的点
Let’s summary some shortcomings
# 第一个就是麻花的捏合处没有捏好
First, I did not tight the dough twists up
# 第二个就是锅不够大
Second, the pot is not large enough
# 如果锅够大的话
If I have a large pot
# 麻花是比较直立的
The twist can be straight
# 现在它是这么有点弯的
Now, it curved a little bit
# 所以说 如果下次可以的话
So for the next time
# 我们要买一个更大的锅
We need to buy a bigger pot